我离开了我的爱,我的爱我离开
I left my love, my love I left
一个睡在她的床上
A-sleeping in her bed
我转过身去对我的真爱
I turned my back on my true love
去战斗约翰尼Reb
Went fighting Johnny Reb
我把我的爱一封信
I left my love a letter
在发牢骚的一棵树
In the holler of a tree
我告诉她她会找到我
I told her she would find me
在美国骑兵
In the US Cavalry
你好哦,下来他们去
Hi-ho, down they go
没有这样的词是“不能”
There's no such word as "can't"
我们将骑清洁降到地狱和背部
We'll ride clean down to hell and back
尤利西斯格兰特的辛普森
For Ulysses Simpson Grant
你好哦,下来他们去
Hi-ho, down they go
没有这样的词是“不能”
There's no such word as "can't"
我们将骑清洁降到地狱和背部
We'll ride clean down to hell and back
尤利西斯格兰特的辛普森
For Ulysses Simpson Grant
我离开了我的爱,我的爱我离开
I left my love, my love I left
一个睡在她的床上
A-sleeping in her bed
我转过身去对我的真爱
I turned my back on my true love
去战斗约翰尼Reb
Went fighting Johnny Reb
我把我的爱一封信
I left my love a letter
在发牢骚的一棵树
In the holler of a tree
我告诉她她会找到我
I told her she would find me
在美国骑兵
In the US Cavalry
你好哦,下来他们去
Hi-ho, down they go
没有这样的词是“不能”
There's no such word as "can't"
我们将乘坐干净到新奥尔良
We'll ride clean down to New Orleans
尤利西斯格兰特的辛普森
For Ulysses Simpson Grant
一般赫尔伯特,预约。
General Hurlburt, by appointment.
- 一般赫尔伯特和上校马洛。- 史蒂夫,进来。
- General Hurlburt and Colonel Marlowe. - Steve, come in.
你好,萨姆。上校马洛。
Hello, Sam. Colonel Marlowe.
-谢尔曼将军,上校马洛。-你好吗?
- General Sherman, Colonel Marlowe. - How do you do?
马洛,我一直渴望见到你。
Marlowe, I've been anxious to meet you.
- 这是一种特权,先生。-坐下来。
- It's a privilege, sir. - Sit down.
- 这是你第一次看维克斯堡吗?-是的,先生。
- Is this your first look at Vicksburg? - Yes, sir.
我们一直在寻找这十个月,我们不喜欢它。
We've been looking at it for ten months, and we don't like it.
上校,为了你的利益,战争在我们这边还没有顺利在所有。
Colonel, for your benefit, the war on our side hasn't been going well at all.
不是在华盛顿,不是在报纸上,而不是在现场。
Not in Washington, not in the newspapers, not in the field.
说得好听点,以更少的男性和更少的资源,
To put it mildly, with less men and less resources,
南有鞭打我们陷入停滞状态。
the South has whipped us to a standstill.
现在,如果我能把维克斯堡……
Now, if I could take Vicksburg...
整个画面就会改变,但我必须做这个夏天。
the whole picture would change, but I'd have to do it this summer.
或坐在这里一。
Or sit out here another year.
这可能会花费我们100000人。它可能会花费我们一个战争。
Which might cost us 100,000 men. It might cost us a war.
这让这跟他们的主要供应来源,和一根荆棘在我们这边。
Which brings this talk to their main source of supply - and a thorn in our side.
- 牛顿站。- 山姆。
- Newton Station. - Sam.
马洛工作的细节,你的计划很彻底。
Marlowe has worked out the details of your plan pretty thoroughly.
如果我能回到洛杉矶田庄马上,我们可以离开到周四。
If I could get back to La Grange right away, we could leave by Thursday.
好的。你的人是谁?
Good. Who would your people be?
我自己的第一个伊利诺斯州与西科德的第一和第二爱荷华州密歇根。
My own First Illinois with Secord's First Michigan and Second Iowa.
我们会挑选到一个短旅。
We'd be culled down to a short brigade.
横在La田庄,穿过雷普利,新奥尔巴尼,休斯顿……
Cross at La Grange, down through Ripley, New Albany, Houston...
- 有什么错了,先生?- 我知道地图。继续进行。
- Is there something wrong, sir? - I know the map. Proceed.
无论如何,主要的技巧是没有战斗直到我们打牛顿站。
Anyway, the main trick is no fighting until we hit Newton Station.
你多少跟踪图摧毁?
How much track do you figure to destroy?
尽我所能。至少足以让他们忙碌的几个月。
As much as I can. At least enough to keep them busy for a couple of months.
否则,突袭将只是一匹马骑。
Otherwise, the raid would just be another horse ride.
好了,上校,去吧。所有的rails、领带、建筑、桥梁、车辆。
All right, Colonel, go ahead. All the rails, ties, buildings, bridges, rolling stock.
山姆,即使他应该得到通过牛顿站,
Sam, even if he should get through to Newton Station,
他会300英里死点在邦联。
he'd be 300 miles dead centre in the Confederacy.
- 你认为你会怎么回来的?- 有你,先生?
- Have you thought how you'd get back? - Have you, sir?
嗯,我想我问的。
Well, I guess I asked for that.
但是我讨厌想起你坐在在安德森威尔监狱。
But I hate to think of you sitting it out in Andersonville Prison.
- 这是一个藏污纳垢之处。- 我想那两次,太,先生。
- It's a hellhole. - I'd think about that twice, too, sir.
嗯,上校,你的成功。
Well, Colonel, your success.
在洛杉矶的联邦骑兵得宝田庄,田纳西州
THE UNION CAVALRY DEPOT AT LA GRANGE, TENNESSEE
好吧,这是洛杉矶田庄。
All right, here is La Grange.
- 我们将每天35英里,平均。- 35吗?
- We will make 35 miles a day, average. - 35?
35吗?那不是一点夸大它吗?
35? Isn't that stretching it a bit?
这将是第一天,内德。我打算让这个距离的两倍。
It will be the first day, Ned. I intend to make twice that distance.
在这样的军事行动,一切都是拉伸。
In an operation like this, everything is stretched.
现在,只是等我几分钟,约翰。
Now, just hold on a minute, John.
切割男子口粮从五天到三…
Cutting the men's rations from five days to three...
他们必须靠土地最终。他们也要去适应它。
They'll have to live off the land eventually. They might as well get used to it.
他们似乎兴奋。有一个谣言他们前往纳什维尔和游行。
They seem excited. There's a rumour they're headed for Nashville and a parade.
这是一个好的谣言传播,借助军士长。
That was a good rumour to spread, with the help of the Sergeant Major.
- 谢谢你,先生。-和,先生们,
- Thank you, sir. - And, gentlemen,
我得承认,他们也把我给骗了。
I'll have to admit they had me fooled too.
你看,我要用我的离开去做一个小的竞选回家。
You see, I was going to use my leave to do a little electioneering back home.
你知道,摇几手,吻几婴儿。
You know, shake a few hands, kiss a few babies.
你看,我这个秋季竞选国会议员。
You see, I'm running for Congress this fall.
嗯,有30000票在安德森威尔,菲尔。
Well, there's 30,000 votes at Andersonville, Phil.
我希望你不要让任何的动摇他们的手。
I hope you don't get to shake any of their hands.
叶子被取消,订单reshoe整个枯萎的套装,
Leaves are being cancelled, orders to reshoe the whole blasted outfit,
和他们中的一些人甚至还不是闪亮的鞋子。
and some of them shoes ain't even shiny yet.
是的。
Yep.
我想知道发生什么了。他们一直坐在那棵树下所有的早晨。
I'm trying to figure out what's up. They've been sitting under that tree all morning.
我听到一些谣言对我们被拿出一大游行北上。
I heard some scuttlebutt about us being pulled out for a big parade up North.
-我想我们前往纳什维尔。- 这是我喜欢的。
- I figure we're heading for Nashville. - That's to my liking.
游行,然后离开。现在这场战争开始成形。
A parade, and then leave. Now this war is starting to shape up.
- 的军官的会议吗?- 在那棵树下那边的,先生。
- Where's the officers' conference? - Over under that tree yonder, sir.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
- 我的道歉迟到了。- 理解。
- My apologies for being late. - Understood.
- 坐下来,大。-我不认为我知道主要的。
- Sit down, Major. - I don't believe I know the Major.
我很抱歉。上校马洛,主要的假象。
I'm sorry. Colonel Marlowe, Major Kendall.
-你好吗?-很高兴认识你。
- How do you do? - Glad to know you.
主要的肯德尔刚刚被分配到我们格兰特将军。
Major Kendall has just been assigned to us by General Grant.
主要的好像出均匀。你的随身武器,肯德尔吗?
The Major seems to be out of uniform. Where are your side arms, Kendall?
如果你看看这本书,你将会看到一个外科医生不带他们。
If you look in the book, you'll see a surgeon doesn't carry them.
外科医生吗?你剪出我们的大炮和我们的马车。没有什么能将我们拖下来。
Surgeon? You cut out our artillery and our wagons. Nothing to slow us down.
和现在你鞍我们医生和医疗单位吗?
And now you saddle us with a doctor and a medical unit?
法规,约翰。肯德尔一路走来。
Regulations, John. Kendall goes along.
很好,先生。有什么问题吗?
Very well, sir. Any questions?
- 我只能说我很高兴对于一些行动。- 没有荣耀狩猎。
- All I can say is I'm glad for some action. - No glory hunting.
如果任何敲门这体无完肤,这将是一个交火。是吗,先生?
If anything knocks this into a cocked hat, it'll be a firefight. Is that all, sir?
-洛根,是布雷迪准备好了吗?- 哦,一张照片。
- Logan, is Brady ready? - Oh, a photograph.
移开。搬回去。
Move away. Move back.
你准备好我们,布雷迪吗?
Are you ready for us, Brady?
上校。坐下来,上校。
Colonel. Sit down, Colonel.
,非常感谢你。- 没关系。
- Thank you very much. - That's all right.
- 坐下来,马洛。- 没有帽子,请,先生们。
- Sit down, Marlowe. - No hats, please, gentlemen.
这是正确的。好和放松。
That's right. Nice and relaxed.
现在,玫瑰是红色的,紫罗兰是蓝色的,相机的直视你。
Now, roses are red, violets are blue, the camera's looking straight at you.
哦,我必须有另一个。那个男人在穿白大衣的感动。
Oh, I must have another one. That man in the white coat moved.
这不是所有他会动不久。一般,就这些吗?
That isn't all he'll be moving before long. General, is that all?
这就是,先生们。谢谢你,布雷迪。
That's all, gentlemen. Thank you, Brady.
谢谢你,一般。非常感谢你。
Thank you, General. Thank you very much.
坐下来。
Sit down.
上校,我想你不开心我的进展。
Colonel, I gather you're not too happy about my going along.
我没想到在你,这是所有。
I hadn't counted on you, that's all.
我能理解你的原因是试图避免战斗,从战术上来说。
I can understand your reasons for trying to avoid a fight, tactically speaking.
但是你要很深入敌军领地。
But you're going very deep into enemy territory.
告诉我,你打算做什么对你的伤吗?
Tell me, what did you intend to do about your wounded?
我打算搬家,和快速行动。
I intend to move, and move fast.
那些太严重上升进行将留给了敌人的仁慈。
Those too badly shot up to carry on will be left to the clemency of the enemy.
- 民用或军用。- 包括你自己吗?
- Civilian or military. - Including yourself?
自然。
Naturally.
这是一个非常原始的态度。从医学上说。
That's a pretty primitive attitude. Medically speaking.
嗯,医生,战争并不是一个文明的业务。
Well, Doctor, war isn't exactly a civilised business.
当然,我意识到它给你伙计们更广领域的机会……
Of course, I realise that it gives you fellas a wider field of opportunity...
- 实验,上校?- 我没说。
- For experimenting, Colonel? - I didn't say that.
- 米奇。-是的,先生?
- Mitch. - Yes, sir?
- 给医生一个完整的名单。-是的,先生。
- Give the doctor a full roster. - Yes, sir.
检查每一个人。
Examine every man.
扔掉任何男人- 在你不成问题的意见,当然,是不适宜的。
Throw out any man who - in your unchallenged opinion, of course - is unfit.
即使是那些可能生病一个星期从今天。
Even those who might get sick a week from today.
看,我不要求分配给这个任务。
Look, I didn't ask to be assigned to this mission.
我是一名军医。我被命令去,我要去做我的工作。
I'm a military doctor. I've been ordered to go and I'm going to do my job.
所以我罗嗦。
So get off my back.
-喇叭手!-是的,先生?
- Bugler! - Yes, sir?
- 让我米切尔。- 军士长米切尔在医院。
- Get me Mitchell. - Sergeant Major Mitchell's in the hospital.
- 你多大了?- 32,先生。
- How old are you? - 32, sir.
加入这个群体。
Join that group.
挂在,儿子。我们开始吧。
Hang on, son. Here we go.
这将伤害更糟。
This is going to hurt worse.
那里。他会好的。
There. He'll be all right.
- 我有你生病的列表,假象。- 好的。我很高兴这是一个短的。
- I got your sick list, Kendall. - Good. I'm glad it's a short one.
我们会让水满出来。
We'll let that drain full out.
- 我赞成了,医生。- 小家伙很沸腾。
- I approve of that, Doctor. - The lad had quite a boil.
我没有来这里看你雕刻人的后面。
I didn't come here to watch you carving anybody's behind.
- 为什么是米切尔的名字在这个列表吗?- 先生,我们观察到在这里安静。
- Why's Mitchell's name on that list? - Sir, we observe quiet here.
- 这是什么?- 吸毒成瘾者,这是上校马洛。
- What's this? - Hoppy, this is Colonel Marlowe.
你怎么做的?排队。我们将照顾你现。
How do you do? Stand in line. We'll take care of you presently.
- 是他和我们一起去吗?- 他是一个好男人。我需要他。
- Is he going with us? - He's a good man. I need him.
- 我需要米切尔。他的强壮如牛。- 让我看什么。
- I need Mitchell. He's strong as a bull. - Let me show you something.
上校,我一直试图告诉医生,这是没有什么不寻常的。
Colonel, I've been trying to tell the doctor that this is nothing unusual.
不是因为一个男人与疟疾。
Not for a man with malaria.
没有什么新的,假象。
There's nothing new about this, Kendall.
我看见他骑在一天40英里,瑟瑟发抖。
I've seen him ride 40 miles in one day, shivering.
- 他总是疟疾。- 所以你赞成我的诊断。
- He always gets malaria. - So you concur in my diagnosis.
米奇,离开床。我有一些威士忌。
Mitch, get out of bed. I got some whiskey.
你们呆在原地,警官。
You stay where you are, Sergeant.
我被要求脱值勤表任何一个男人,在我看来是不适宜的。
I was ordered to take off the duty roster any man who in my opinion was unfit.
他生病了,他要呆在这里。那些是我的订单。
He's sick and he's going to stay here. Those are my orders.
你已经读了整本书,你没有吗?
You've read the whole book, haven't you?
哦,上校!
Oh, Colonel!
我们得到那小伙子与所有这些对你的条纹。
We got that fella with all them stripes for you.
- 给他带来。- 我们把他马上火车。
- Bring him in. - We hauled him right off the train.
- 军士Kirby报告,先生。-嗯,科比。
- Sergeant Kirby reporting, sir. - Well, Kirby.
除了喝醉了,有什么让你愤怒吗?
Besides being drunk, what's got you riled up?
他们让我在城里。把我拉下了火车。
They got me in town. Pulled me off the train.
只是变得充满。我第一次在两。
Just gotten filled. My first in two years.
他们告诉我你是好的。你最好是。
They tell me you're good. You better be.
你更换最好的士兵在团。
You're replacing the best soldier in the regiment.
- 我希望你是高兴的。- 我可以快乐的我要去哪里。
- I expect you to be happy about that. - I could be happier where I was going.
- 你把我搞糊涂了。- 不,先生,你让我来了。
- You got me there. - No, sir, you got me here.
- 先生。先生。
- Sir. - Sir.
3月这军士到河边,把他扔在。
March this sergeant to the river and throw him in.
- 衣服和所有吗?- 衣服和所有。
- Clothes and all? - Clothes and all.
泵他充满黑咖啡直到耗尽他的耳朵。
Pump him full of black coffee till it runs out his ears.
科比,当你回来,回来冷静。你有两个小时。
Kirby, when you come back, come back sober. You've got two hours.
- 游行,纳什维尔……- 你可以离开那个小桶。
- Parades, Nashville... - You can leave that keg.
欢迎你到…先生。
You're welcome to it... sir.
与我纠缠,我要你的隐藏。
Tangle with me and I'll have your hide.
欢迎你,太,先生。如果它在值勤。
You're welcome to that too, sir. If it's in the line of duty.
- 向前,离开!- 向前,离开!
- Forward, left! - Forward, left!
- 哟哦!- 哟哦!
- Yo-oh! - Yo-oh!
我离开了我的爱我的爱我离开,一个睡在她的床上
I left my love My love I left, a-sleeping in her bed
我转过身去对我的真爱去战斗约翰尼犹太人的尊称
I turned my back on my true love Went fighting Johnny Reb
我把我的爱一封信在叫喊的树……
I left my love a letter in the holler of a tree...
- 祝你好运,约翰。- 谢谢你,先生。
- Good luck, John. - Thank you, sir.
你好哦,下来他们就没有这样的词是“不能”
Hi-ho, down they go There's no such word as "can't"
我们将骑清洁降到地狱和回尤利西斯・辛普森格兰特
We'll ride clean down to hell and back for Ulysses Simpson Grant
我把我的爱一封信在叫喊的一棵树
I left my love a letter in the holler of a tree
我告诉她她会找到我在美国骑兵
I told her she would find me in the US Cavalry
在美国骑兵
In the US Cavalry
你好哦,下来他们就没有这样的词是“不能”
Hi-ho, down they go There's no such word as "can't"
我们将乘坐干净到新奥尔良
We'll ride clean down to New Orleans
尤利西斯格兰特的辛普森
For Ulysses Simpson Grant
我离开了我的爱我的爱我离开
I left my love My love I left
一个睡在她的床上
A-sleeping in her bed
在这里等待一分钟。
Wait on here a minute.
- 太阳,它提出了在东每次吗?- 它肯定是在密苏里州。
- The sun, it raises in the east every time? - It sure does in Missouri.
八小时,不转,我们一直朝着这个方向发展。
For eight hours, with no turning, we've been heading this way.
如果太阳在东方提出,什么方向?
If the sun raises in the east, what direction is that?
- 这不是北。- 当然不是。这是南。
- It ain't north. - Course not. It's south.
我们已经骑不偏不倚的篮板球的领土。
We've been riding smack-dab into reb territory.
- 篮板球的国家,理查德。-是的,先生。
- Reb country, Richard. - Yes, sir.
发送你的球探。
Send out your scouts.
你去叫一个暂停,或让他们的敌人的仁慈?
Are you going to call a halt, or leave them to the clemency of the enemy?
声音回忆。
Sound recall.
只是一个巡逻,先生。没有迹象表明任何主要的力量,只要我可以告诉。
Just a patrol, sir. No sign of any major force, as far as I could tell.
事实上我们已经发现了。
The fact remains we've been spotted.
这个词现在已经确定。他们会回来这里一切可用的。
The word's out for sure now. They'll be back here with everything available.
好吧,内德,你可以准备回头。
All right, Ned, you can prepare to turn back.
这是一个很严重的错误,约翰,把力。
That's a bad mistake, John, splitting the force.
现在你需要每个人你有。该死的转移。
Now you need every man you've got. Diversion be damned.
- 他们必须想我们都退后。- 哦,当然,当然。
- They've got to think we all turned back. - Oh, sure, sure.
但从现在起,每个约翰尼Reb用枪将隐藏在树后面
But from now on, every Johnny Reb with a gun will be hiding behind a tree
想让自己出名。
trying to make a name for himself.
和你想减少力的三分之一!约翰,听我说。
And you want to cut your force by one third! John, listen to me.
有一个古老的公理在政治:你永远不会把你的选票……
There's an old axiom in politics: You never split your ballot...
理查德,当马是浇水和男人是美联储,我们就搬出去。
Richard, when the horses are watered and the men are fed, we'll move out.
嘿,医生。
Hey, Doctor.
这些孩子们说这里有什么违禁品错在那个小屋。
These here contraband children say there's something wrong at that cabin.
我想他们需要一个医生。
I guess they need a doctor.
所有的权利。
All right.
- 你是医生吗?- 是的,我是。
- Are you the doctor? - Yes, I am.
发生了什么事?
What happened?
这是Rainey先生,先生。雷尼第一。他死了。
It's Rainey, sir. Rainey the first. He's dead.
继续。
Carry on.
那里的假象?
Where's Kendall?
肯德尔博士走过去,一些轻的有色人种的小木屋。
Dr Kendall went over to that cabin with some young coloured people.
- 紧急,我相信。- 他什么? !
- An emergency, I believe. - He what?!
他走过去,一些轻的有色人种的小木屋。
He went over to that cabin with some young coloured people.
- 你是医生吗?-什么?不,不。
- Are you the doctor too? - What? No, no.
肯德尔,你在搞什么鬼?
Kendall, what the devil are you doing?
我们只是交付一个婴儿。
We just delivered a baby.
这是一个小女孩。
It's a little girl.
你可以照顾她的现在,奶奶。
You can take care of her now, Granny.
你将会好起来的。
You're going to be all right.
我们有几个受伤的男人,你知道的。
We've got a couple of wounded men out there, you know.
没有,一个人的死亡。
No, one's dead.
一个走了,一个人的出生。
One's gone, one's born.
这是一个神奇的过程,不是吗?
It's an amazing process, isn't it?
多达我已经交付,它总能让我敬畏。
As many as I've delivered, it never fails to awe me.
好吧,孩子,你有一个新妹妹。进去,看看她。
All right, children, you got a new sister. Go in, take a look at her.
好吧,假象。回去照顾你的受伤。
All right, Kendall. Go back and take care of your wounded.
他们会好的。霍普金斯知道要做什么。
They'll be all right. Hopkins knows what to do.
你不是一个国家的外科医生。你是一个军官在联邦军队宣誓。
You're not a country sawbones. You're an officer in the Union Army under oath.
我把一个旧誓言之前。
I took an older oath before that one.
他们似乎并不会有任何麻烦的婴儿在这附近。
They didn't seem to be having any trouble having babies around here before.
我被要求帮助,我无法把它们放下。住口。即使你出生。
I was asked to help and I couldn't turn 'em down. Come off it. Even you were born.
现在,你是在军官的逮捕。
As of now, you are under officer's arrest.
不服从。
Insubordination.
- 我仍然执行我的职责,先生?- 从现在开始限制他们的军队。
- Do I still carry out my duties, sir? - From now on confine them to the troops.
很好,先生。
Very well, sir.
别欺人太甚,假象。
Don't push me too far, Kendall.
前进!
Forward!
Lukey,狗提高如此大惊小怪?
Lukey, what are the dogs raising such a fuss about?
狗吗?你知道狗大惊小怪。
Dogs? You know how dogs make such a fuss.
- 士兵、想念汉娜。很多他们。- 士兵?多么美妙!
- Soldiers, Miss Hannah. Lots of 'em. - Soldiers? How wonderful!
雷声在外屋。他们的洋基队。
Thunder in the outhouse. Them's Yankees.
Lukey,你去楼下并满足他们。
Lukey, you go on downstairs and meet them.
Lukey,你听到了吗?
Lukey, do you hear?
来这里,女孩。
Come here, girl.
来吧。
Come on.
- 谁住在这里?- 汉娜小姐猎人住在这里。
- Who lives here? - Miss Hannah Hunter lives here.
告诉她我想见到她。上校马洛,联盟军队。
Tell her I want to see her. Colonel Marlowe, Union Army.
是的,先生。
Yes, sir.
把枪放下。
Put that gun away.
- 对不起,这种入侵,夫人。- 这并不是说,上校。
- Sorry for this intrusion, ma'am. - It isn't that, Colonel.
只是我从来没有准备自己看到统一的围墙内这房子。
It's just that I never prepared myself to see that uniform within the walls of this house.
夫人,我们没有更多的希望在这里比你有我们。
Ma'am, we no more wish to be here than you do to have us.
为什么,那是勇敢地说,上校。
Why, that's gallantly spoken, Colonel.
不管发生什么我们的分歧,我担心我忘记了设施。
No matter what our differences, I fear I'm forgetting the amenities.
- 欢迎来到Greenbriar,先生们。- 谢谢你。
- Welcome to Greenbriar, gentlemen. - Thank you.
Lukey,以君子的帽子。
Lukey, take the gentlemen's hats.
- 军士科比。- 军士。
- Sergeant Kirby. - Sergeant.
太太。
Ma'am.
嗯,我们要让自己更舒服的玫瑰的房间吗?
Well, shall we make ourselves more comfortable in the Rose Room?
不,谢谢你,夫人。我们只呆一会儿。
No, thank you, ma'am. We'll only stay a moment.
你和你的男人骑在吗?
You and your men are riding on?
不,我们将在你的森林里露营过夜。
No, we will bivouac in your woods for the night.
睡在冰冷的地面吗?
Sleeping on the cold, cold ground?
当这是可怕的,浪费的,可怕的斗争正在结束,上校?
When is this awful, wasteful, terrible struggle going to end, Colonel?
哥哥对弟弟……
Brother against brother...
和在我们逗留期间,没有人会被允许离开前提。
And during our stay no one will be allowed to leave the premises.
无论我们是否去,上校?
Wherever would we go, Colonel?
我相信你必须同意这场战争使得对每个人都孤独。
I'm sure you must agree that this war makes loneliness for everyone.
同时,我必须征用大部分的谷物和马,如果您有任何。
Also, I must commandeer most of the grain and horses, if you have any.
你将会支付,小姐猎人,一切事情,在联盟的美元。
You will be paid, Miss Hunter, for everything, in Union greenbacks.
我们不会打扰你了。晚上好。
We will not bother you any longer. Good evening.
- 科比。- 请原谅,夫人。
- Kirby. - By your leave, ma'am.
汉娜猎人,怎么抓住你,说话像一个字段的手吗?你呼叫,我们无存。
Hannah Hunter, what's got hold of you, talking like a field hand? You alls, we alls.
洋基队!
Yankees!
这是不可思议的,上校。
It's uncanny, Colonel.
我听说过他们,但我不相信它。
I've heard about 'em, but I didn't believe it.
我收到我的佣金从密歇根州州长!
I received my commission from the Governor of Michigan!
- 轻人……- 你有什么问题吗?
- Young man... - What's your question?
问题是这个男人的权威在他现在的位置。
The question is this man's authority in his present position.
像往常一样,我想现在的生活的严峻现实。
As usual, I am trying to present the grim facts of life.
他不明白,咖啡口味更好
He doesn't understand that coffee tastes better
如果厕所挖下游代替上游。
if the latrines are dug downstream instead of upstream.
你喜欢怎样的咖啡,上校?
How do you like your coffee, Colonel?
- 西科德,你需要…- 原谅。
- Secord, you oughta... - Pardon.
上校!上校马洛!
Colonel! Colonel Marlowe!
我忘记我的礼貌。为什么,我有没有……
I am forgetting my manners. Why, how I ever...
嗯,我不相信我遇到的这些先生们。
Well, I don't believe I've met these gentlemen.
亨特小姐。西科德上校。主要的灰色。主要的假象。
Miss Hunter. Colonel Secord. Major Gray. Major Kendall.
太太。
Ma'am.
我只是如此的仓促。
I'm just so scatterbrained.
可怜的爸爸和妈妈必须翻在我在坟墓里
Poor Papa and Mama must be turning over in their graves at me
没有什么Greenbriar扩展小酒店可以提供。
for not extending what little hospitality Greenbriar can offer.
至少我可以邀请你共进晚餐。
At least I can extend an invitation to you for dinner.
- 不,小姐猎人……我坚持。
- No, Miss Hunter... - I insist.
有三个胖capons,不得不去无论如何。
There's three fat capons that have to go anyhow.
与我们的商店什么粮食被减少了,就像你说的。
What with our store of grain being reduced, like you mentioned.
所以,你看,你带来了它自己,不是吗?
So, you see, you brought it on yourself, didn't you?
对我而言,我将会很高兴…
Speaking for myself, I would be delighted...
很好,谢谢你。热的食物很难拒绝。
Very well, thank you. Hot food is pretty hard to turn down.
灿烂的。现在,我能指望有多少?
Splendid. Now, how many can I count on?
- 将五或六是……?- 不。
- Would five or six be...? - Not at all.
不同凡响的。
Perfectly wonderful.
九点,先生们?
At nine, gentlemen?
- 德上校?- 第一个密歇根,夫人。
- Colonel Secord? - Of the First Michigan, ma'am.
- 主要的灰色?- 夫人。
- Major Gray? - Ma'am.
主要的……肯德尔,不是吗?
Major... Kendall, isn't it?
恐怕我得遗憾,夫人。这不是我的选择,我向你保证。
I'm afraid I'll have to regret, ma'am. It's not of my choice, I assure you.
此刻,我被逮捕。
At the moment, I'm under arrest.
我们都将很高兴接受邀请,小姐猎人。
We will all be glad to accept the invitation, Miss Hunter.
太太?
Ma'am?
你把你的手帕。
You dropped your handkerchief.
- 关心多一点,西科德上校?-不,谢谢你,夫人。
- Care for a little more, Colonel Secord? - No, thank you, ma'am.
上校马洛吗?
Colonel Marlowe?
-不,谢谢你。- 来了,上校。
- No, thank you. - Come now, Colonel.
一个男人与一个像你一样的大框架不能啃掉像个小老山雀。
A man with a big frame like yours can't just nibble away like a little old titmouse.
先生们,请就座。
Gentlemen, please be seated.
现在,什么是你的偏好?腿……或乳房吗?
Now, what was your preference? The leg... or the breast?
我已经很足够的两个,谢谢。
I've had quite enough of both, thank you.
真遗憾。
What a shame.
- 将别人想要一点吗?-不,谢谢你。
- Would anyone else like some more? - No, thank you.
先生们,坐下。我必须警告你太,没有咖啡。
Gentlemen, be seated. I must warn you too, there's no coffee.
和一个甜或任何种类的甜点是不可能的。
And a sweet or a dessert of any kind was just out of the question.
糖的每桶150美元。
Sugar's $150 a barrel.
“但你的公平的话语作过甜如糖,
"And yet your fair discourse hath been as sweet as sugar,
使艰辛和美味的甜蜜。”
making the hard way sweet and delectable."
多么完美地迷人。有点自己的东西吗?
How perfectly charming. A little something of your own?
不,夫人。理查德二世。
No, ma'am. Richard II.
- 在职业上,我是一个演员。- 为什么,多么的迷人!
- By profession, I'm an actor. - Why, how fascinating!
为什么,你的雪茄主要肯德尔。先生们,请就座。
Why, Major Kendall, your cigar. Gentlemen, please be seated.
主要的肯德尔医生。和德上校几乎一个国会议员。
Major Kendall a doctor. And Colonel Secord almost a congressman.
和你一个演员。现在所有的军人。
And you an actor. And now all military men.
这样的浪费人才。
Such a waste of talent.
但是,当然,上校马洛,我想象你是一个职业军人。
But, of course, Colonel Marlowe, I imagine that you are a professional soldier.
不,在这之前,我是一个疯狂的铁路工程师。
No, prior to this insanity, I was a railroad engineer.
为什么,怎么激动。
Why, how thrilling.
想能够引导其中的一个巨大的东西,膨化和热气腾腾的。
To think of being able to steer one of those huge things, puffing and steaming.
响,小铃。叮咚!叮咚!
Ringing that little bell. Ding-dong! Ding-dong!
不完全。我的工作是在铁路的建造。
Not quite. My job was in the construction of railroads.
为什么,我的!这样杰出的思想。
Why, my! Such brilliant minds.
可怜的我几乎挤过朗斯特里特的神学院为女士小姐。
Poor little me barely squeezed through Miss Longstreet's Seminary for Ladies.
你是怎样设法记住所有的这些书在大学吗?
How did you ever manage to remember all those books in college?
我没有。我开始开车铁路在10美分一天峰值和发现。
I didn't. I started driving rail spikes at ten cents a day and found.
现在,我必须要问小姐猎人,你离开我们。
And now, Miss Hunter, I must ask you to leave us.
我们正在使用这个房间的特权一两个小时。如果我们可以。
We are taking the privilege of using this room for an hour or two. If we may.
当然,但你不喜欢使用另一个房间吗?这项研究,也许?
Of course, but wouldn't you prefer using another room? The study, perhaps?
我们这里很舒服。
We're quite comfortable here.
我很抱歉,但是我必须粗鲁和解释。
I'm sorry but I must be rude and explain.
和我必须在Lukey字段在早上5。
Lukey and I must be in the fields by five in the morning.
先生们,继续照亮你的雪茄。
Gentlemen, go ahead and light your cigars.
- 请允许我。- 谢谢你。
- Allow me. - Thank you kindly.
这一切和盘子之前必须完成她能上床睡觉。
All this and the dishes must be done before she can get to bed.
-我是不是太不体谅吗?- 当然不,夫人。
- Am I being too inconsiderate? - Of course not, ma'am.
- 我可以吗?- 当然。这样,先生们。
- May I? - Of course. This way, gentlemen.
多么美妙。
How wonderful.
真的,我认为这是一个迷人的晚餐。
Really, I thought it was a charming dinner.
- 把这房间。-是的,先生。
- Post this room. - Yes, sir.
- 我希望你能舒适的在这里。-哦,是的。这是好。
- I hope you'll be comfortable here. - Oh, yes. This is fine.
- 如果你想生火,它准备好了。- 不,它很好。
- If you wish to light a fire, it's ready. - No, it's fine.
- 一些白兰地。我要把它Lukey。-不,谢谢你,没有白兰地。
- Some brandy. I'll have Lukey bring it. - No, thank you, no brandy.
你确定这里没有更多的我可以…
Are you sure there's nothing more that I can...
哦,是的。
Oh, yes.
医生,没有必要为你加入这个。
Doctor, there's no need for you to be a part of this.
也许会给你一些小姐猎人Greenbriar为主。
Perhaps Miss Hunter would show you some of the beauties of Greenbriar.
- 为什么,当然,如果他有任何兴趣……- 他会很高兴。
- Why, of course, if he has any interest... - He'd be pleased to.
很好。那么,来吧,医生。
Very well. Come, then, Doctor.
我注意到一个漂亮的花园。我们去散步吗?
I noticed a lovely garden. Shall we take a stroll?
为什么,当然。
Why, of course.
你知道,你先生们必须舒服的沉重的制服,
You know, you gentlemen must be comfortable in your heavy uniforms,
但是我觉得一个明确的寒意在空气中- 这是我和我的薄血。
but I feel a definite chill in the air - it's me and my thin blood.
对不起,我去请个披肩吗?
Would you excuse me while I go and fetch a shawl?
亨特小姐。- 是的,专业?
- Miss Hunter. - Yes, Major?
恐怕我要和你一起去。
I'm afraid I'll have to go with you.
搬到楼上去吗?和我在一起吗?
Upstairs? With me?
- 为什么,专业!- 你只能得到一个披肩。
- Why, Major! - You're only getting a shawl.
当然,但是在这些地区,真是前所未闻的……
Of course, but in these parts it's unheard of...
这是告诉你的孙子。
It's something to tell your grandchildren.
这是战争。目前,Greenbriar是一个军事设施。
This is war. At the moment, Greenbriar is a military installation.
我不认为有任何真正的伤害,是,你是一个医生。
I don't suppose there's any real harm, being that you're a doctor.
这是正确的。
That's right.
Lukey,带一些白兰地,我的客厅,请。
Lukey, bring some brandy to my sitting room, please.
- 我希望你能舒适的在这里,主要的。- 谢谢你。
- I hope you'll be comfortable here, Major. - Thank you.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
嘿!你要去哪里吗?
Hey! Where are you going with that?
- 汉娜小姐要求这白兰地。- 我知道,为主要的。
- Miss Hannah asked for this brandy. - I know, for the Major.
我们从来没有给我们任何一个一流的官员一个未标记的瓶子,
We never give any of our top-ranking officers an unlabelled bottle,
除非有人品味它第一。
unless somebody tastes it first.
- 这是你吗?测试的事情吗?- 当然。
- Is this what you does? Test things? - Certainly.
看到第二条?这意味着我正式为专业品酒师上。
See that second stripe? That means I'm official taster for majors on up.
这里是洛杉矶田庄。
Here's La Grange.
我们已经下到这里大约80英里。
We've come down here approximately 80 miles.
- 我们正走向牛顿站。- 任何字在敌人的力量吗?
- We're headed for Newton Station. - Any word on the enemy strength there?
不,不是一个词。不管它是什么,我们不得不把它。
No, not a word. Whatever it is, we're obliged to take it on.
- 好的。也许我们会看到行动。- 这不是角色扮演游戏。
- Good. Maybe we'll see action. - This is not play-acting.
- 这是你的白兰地,先生。-哦,谢谢。
- Here's your brandy, sir. - Oh, thank you.
- 这是所有测试。- 测试?
- It's all tested. - Tested?
楼下的人,与那些试验机的条纹,因为专业上。
By the man downstairs with those tester's stripes, for majors on up.
哦,是的。中士科比。
Oh, yes. Sergeant Kirby.
- 他真的测试它,不是吗?-是的,先生。两次。
- He really tested it, didn't he? - Yes, sir. Twice.
- Lukey吗? - 是的,想念汉娜。
- Lukey? - Yes, Miss Hannah.
对不起,先生。
Excuse me, sir.
…非常幸运。
... very lucky.
这是下一个信息。我们不会回到洛杉矶田庄。
That is the next piece of information. We're not going back to La Grange.
- 我们什么?- 我们不回去北。
- We're what? - We're not going back north.
我们向南到巴吞鲁日加入了工会力量。
We're heading south to Baton Rouge to join up with the Union forces there.
- 伟大的斯科特,你什么时候决定?- 这是最好的方式。这是唯一的方法。
- Great Scott, when did you decide that? - It's the best way. It's the only way.
约翰,这是300英里从牛顿站到巴吞鲁日。
John, it is 300 miles from Newton Station to Baton Rouge.
和它是300英里从牛顿站到洛杉矶田庄。
And it is 300 miles from Newton Station to La Grange.
只有个篮板真的会一直在我们身后关闭,准备咀嚼我们位。
Only the rebs will really have been closed in behind us, ready to chew us to bits.
所以我们就出去他们至少期望:直南。
So we'll go out the way they least expect: Straight south.
该死的,这是自杀。有可能你的订单可能会被误解?
Damn it, it's suicide. Is it possible your orders could have been misinterpreted?
我唯一的责任后牛顿站
My only duty after Newton Station
是获取尽可能多的这些人我能活着回来。
is to get as many of these men back alive as I can.
所以我仍然必须抗议。
And so I still must protest.
更重要的是,我要在记录一般赫尔伯特。
What's more, I want that on the record for General Hurlburt.
这是冲动的集体自杀。
It is impetuous mass suicide.
它在记录,但得到这个。
It's on the record, but get this.
除非敌人的动作让你接替我的位置,这也将是。
Unless enemy action allows you to take my place, that's the way it will be.
吹牛顿站从地图上,然后到巴吞鲁日。
Blow Newton Station off the map, then through to Baton Rouge.
不会有变化。你明白吗?
There will be no change. Do you understand?
好吧,你在命令。
All right, you're in command.
现在让我们再复习一下。直通到巴吞鲁日。
Now let's go over it again. Straight through to Baton Rouge.
我们不会回头。
We will not turn back.
对不起,让你久等了。是白兰地满意吗?
Sorry for keeping you waiting. Was the brandy satisfactory?
-优秀的。你不和我一起吗?- 善我,没有。我从来没有触摸的精神。
- Excellent. Won't you join me? - Goodness me, no. I never touch spirits.
我的爸爸告诉我,一个女孩应该保持对她的她的智慧在任何时候。
My papa taught me that a girl ought to keep her wits about her at all times.
你的父亲提出了一个非常聪明的女孩。
Your father raised a very smart girl.
你是甜的。你愿意看到花园吗?
You're being sweet. Would you like to see the garden?
你没有忘记你的披肩吗?
Didn't you forget your shawl?
为什么,Lukey !
Why, Lukey!
现在,,你把这盘Lukey下楼,去做你必须做的事。
Now, Lukey, you take that tray downstairs and go about doing what you have to do.
你知道,我记得我第一次尝试的精神,在州长的球在杰克逊。
You know, I remember the first time I tried spirits, at the Governor's Ball in Jackson.
我的护卫,亚当色鬼比洛克西,好吧,从他给了我一个薄荷朱利酒。
My escort, Adam Lovelace from Biloxi, well, he gave me a mint julep.
你知道,那些色鬼男孩都很帅,但很快,
You know, those Lovelace boys are all very handsome, but fast,
如果你知道我的意思。
if you know what I mean.
如果我能告诉你的想法,继续在我的脑海里,一个冰镇薄荷酒之后……我的!
If I could tell you the thoughts that went on in my mind after that one julep... My!
我宁愿知道的想法在你的头脑去现在。
I'd rather know the thoughts going on in your mind right now.
-肯德尔,存的什么……?- 对不起我们不得不中断。
- Kendall, what in the name of...? - Sorry we have to interrupt.
问他们什么他们认为你的机会
Ask them what they think your chances are
炸毁牛顿站和到达巴吞鲁日。
of blowing up Newton Station and getting to Baton Rouge.
- 你是喝醉了吗?- 不幸的是,没有。
- Are you drunk? - Unfortunately, no.
他们倾听楼上。
They were listening upstairs.
使一个不错的听诊器。
Makes a pretty good stethoscope.
不要感到内疚。我也能及时发现。
Don't feel guilty. I was slow to catch on too.
你在哪里,肯德尔吗?
Where were you, Kendall?
嗯,一个绅士认为前两次窥视女人的卧室,
Well, a gentlemen thinks twice before peeking into a lady's bedroom,
但有时它有回报。
but sometimes it pays off.
看起来像她欺骗了我们俩。
Looks like she's made a fool out of both of us.
叮咚。叮咚。
Ding-dong. Ding-dong.
你知道吗,小姐猎人吗?
You know something, Miss Hunter?
你把我一个相当不便。
You have put me to quite an inconvenience.
至少我已经完成了一些东西,先生。
At least I've accomplished something, sir.
我不认为我能接受你的词不讨论这个荣誉与任何人。
I don't suppose I could accept your word of honour not to discuss this with anyone.
- 我不坚持荣誉与任何洋基。- 到底。
- I don't hold to honour with any Yankees. - Exactly.
所以整个密西西比会接到通知。
So the whole state of Mississippi will be alerted.
所以你能建议我应该做什么吗?
So could you possibly suggest what I should do with you?
我注意到她正在在你的神经。现在你的机会向她开枪。
I noticed she was getting on your nerves. Now's your chance to shoot her.
- 一个字从你……- 去吧。向我们射击。
- One more word out of you... - Go ahead. Shoot us.
拍摄我们俩。
Shoot both of us.
但是你永远不会摆脱你的肮脏,谋杀计划,上校先生马洛。
But you'll never get away with your filthy, murdering plans, Mr. Colonel Marlowe.
你和你的神圣原则洋储蓄工会。
You Yankees and your holy principle about saving the Union.
你是海盗掠夺,这就是。
You're plundering pirates, that's what.
你认为没有南方联盟军队,你要去哪里吗?
You think there's no Confederate army where you're going?
你认为我们的男孩在这里睡着了?
Do you think our boys are asleep down here?
他们会赶上你和他们会削减你的碎片,
They'll catch up to you and they'll cut you to pieces,
你无名,孤儿人渣!
you nameless, fatherless scum!
我希望我能在那里看到它。
And I wish I could be there to see it.
如果它发生,小姐猎人,你将。
If it happens, Miss Hunter, you will be.
快点。
Hurry it up.
所有的权利。
All right.
你是一个优秀的骑手,小姐猎人。
You're an excellent rider, Miss Hunter.
有趣的国家,不是吗?
Interesting country, isn't it?
我更感兴趣的是,为什么你汪达尔人没收了我的死去的父亲的衣服。
I'm more interested in why you vandals confiscated my dead father's clothes.
嗯,他们为我们的学员。
Well, they're for our cadets.
-童子军。-童子军!
- Scouts. - Scouts!
间谍,你的意思。
Spies, you mean.
这是一个想知道他们不爬行腹部像蛇。
It's a wonder they don't crawl along on their bellies like snakes.
你会发现下面发生了什么间谍。
You'll find out what happens to spies down here.
我个人的经验是有限的,间谍我只知道一个。
My personal experience with spies is limited. I've only known one.
你介意,专业?我更喜欢独自骑。
Do you mind, Major? I prefer to ride alone.
太太。
Ma'am.
想念汉娜!
Miss Hannah!
好吧,前进!哟哦!
All right, forward! Yo-oh!
回线,医生。
Back in line, Doctor.
- 这些女士的抽屉几乎是干的。- 是的。
- These lady's drawers are almost dry. - Yeah.
你不让寒冷的吗?
Aren't you getting chilly?
不要告诉我你是关心我的健康。
Don't tell me you're concerned about my health.
如果我给你回你的衣服,你可以保证不逃走了吗?
If I give you back your clothes, will you promise not to run away again?
我将,夫人。有一种观点是骄傲成为不切实际的。
I would, ma'am. There's a point where pride becomes impractical.
事实上,如果你能得到一个看你自己,我认为你会同意的。
Actually, if you could get a look at yourself, I'd think you'd agree.
很好。我希望保持我的健康。
Very well. I do wish to keep my health.
- 我不会试图逃跑再次。-你的话的荣誉吗?
- I shall not try to run away again. - Your word of honour?
- 我的字的荣誉。- 洋基?
- My word of honour. - To Yankees?
- 洋基。- 你发誓?
- To Yankees. - Cross your heart?
- 我对你的承诺!- 好吧,Lukey。
- I gave you my word! - All right, Lukey.
亨特小姐和她的衣服帮助。
Help Miss Hunter with her clothes.
我很高兴你是明智的。你开始担心我。
I'm glad you're being sensible. You were beginning to worry me.
- 从医学角度。- 谢谢你,医生。
- From a medical standpoint. - Thank you, Doctor.
我希望我能有进一步的援助,但是你有你自己的南部人帮助。
I wish I could be of further assistance, but you Southern people have your own help.
注意!眼睛看前面!
Attention! Eyes front!
个篮板,先生!
Rebs, sir!
跳跃,河岸。一个完整的旅,会很快来临。
Hopping that riverbank. A full brigade, coming fast.
马,脚和火炮,先生。这不是民兵,无论是。
Horse, foot and artillery, sir. It ain't militia, neither.
- 有多远?- 十分钟。
- How far? - Ten minutes.
好吧,离开视线,得到在这些树。
All right, get out of sight, get in those trees.
敌人的巡逻队。带盖和阻塞。
Enemy patrol. Take cover and choke up.
-喇叭手!- 不是号手,你个白痴!手势信号。
- Bugler! - Not bugler, you idiot! Hand signals.
敌人过河。搬出去。保持安静。
Enemy across the river. Move out. Keep it quiet.
他为什么不站出来战斗吗?他有一个完整的旅。
Why doesn't he stand and fight? He's got a full brigade.
好哇!好哇!对于南方的权利,万岁!
Hurrah! Hurrah! For Southern rights, hurrah!
欢呼,为美丽的蓝色旗帜,熊一个明星
Hurrah for the Bonnie Blue Flag That bears a single star
好哇!好哇!对于南方的权利,万岁!
Hurrah! Hurrah! For Southern rights, hurrah!
欢呼,为美丽的蓝色旗帜,熊一个明星
Hurrah for the Bonnie Blue Flag That bears a single star
- 放轻松。
- Take it easy.
来吧,停止它。
Come on, stop it.
汉娜!
Hannah!
嘿!的帮助!在这里!
Hey! Help! Over here!
哎哟!
Ouch!
让去与那些牙齿!
Let go with those teeth!
- 我有800人。得到了一些水。
- I've got 800 men out there. - Get some water.
似乎所有明确过河。
Looks to be all clear across the river.
嗯…
Well...
有多少男人才能保持一个单身女安静?
How many men does it take to keep one lone female quiet?
上校,犯人想和你谈谈。
Colonel, the prisoner would like a word with you.
是的,小姐猎人吗?
Yes, Miss Hunter?
我在这里不是要抱怨你做了些什么。
I'm not here to complain about what you did.
这是你的责任当你看到它,你做到了。
It was your duty as you saw it, and you did it.
我很抱歉你不得不食言。
I'm sorry you had to break your word.
我给我的字不是为了逃跑。我没有给它不是迫切需要援助。
I gave my word not to run away. I didn't give it not to cry out for assistance.
我想有一个好点,
I suppose there's a fine point there,
但我不得不问你给我你的消息,太。
but I have to ask you to give me your word on that too.
我这样做,在这里和现在。
I do that, here and now.
或者我想当我指证你,我就带着一个破碎的下巴是残疾人。
Or I suppose when I testify against you, I'd be handicapped with a broken jaw.
我这么说。什么,夫人?
I'd say so. Anything else, ma'am?
一个轻微的项目。我忠实的伴侣那里。
One slight item. My constant companions there.
我不知道它是如何在北边,当然,
I don't know how it is up North, of course,
但南方有些时候南方妇女觉得需要隐私。
but down South there are times when Southern women feel the need for privacy.
你们两个。
You two.
我们是尊重。真正的尊重,先生。
We was respectful. Real respectful, sir.
你告诉我们这是好的,只要我们能看到的头顶。
You told us it was all right just as long as we could see the top of her head.
- 你告诉他们吗?- 嗯……
- You told them that? - Well...
然后还有一个项目。
Then there's one more item.
我建议你去看医生。叮咚。叮咚。
I suggest you see a doctor. Ding-dong. Ding-dong.
在那边,谷仓。来吧。
Over there in that barn. Come on.
- 我们是bushwhacked,上校。 - 好吧,烟他们出去。
- We was bushwhacked, Colonel. - All right, smoke 'em out.
保持你的火。
Hold your fire.
嘿,那里!我们结盟,但我们不是敌意。
Hey, there! We're Confederates, but we ain't hostile.
- 诚实的!- 放下武器,快点出来。
- Honest! - Drop your weapons and come on out.
是的,先生。
Yes, sir.
未来。
Coming.
嘿,维吉尔,提前来。
Hey, Virgil, come ahead on.
他们的真正bluebellies。
They's real bluebellies.
看着它,上校。
Watch it, Colonel.
就我们两个人,帽。和一个俘虏。
Just the two of us, Cap. And one captive.
你好,帽。杰基乔和我是抱歉,突然掉你的人。
Howdy, Cap. Jackie Jo and me is sorry about popping away at you people.
我们以为你是更多的警长。
We thought you was more sheriff's deputies.
你有什么对抗警长?
What have you got against sheriff's deputies?
- 这是一个好一个,嗯?- 这是一个光滑的一个。
- That's a good one, huh? - That's a slick one.
我们只是爱警长。
We just love sheriff's deputies.
他们脱离邦联,先生。最低的猪饲养。
They're deserters from the Confederacy, sir. The lowest swine bred.
- 我把它你警长?- 队长亨利与其,退休。
- I take it you're the sheriff? - Captain Henry Goodbody, retired.
代理警长的罗瑞拉县。
Acting sheriff of Lorena County.
我正要逮捕这些老鼠……
I was about to apprehend these rats...
但是我们bushwhacked你,你老山羊,不是吗?
But we bushwhacked you, you old goat, didn't we?
我们这样做,杰基乔。但告诉他们关于我们,Goodyo船长。
That we did, Jackie Jo. But tell them about us, Captain Goodyo.
- 你敢碰他了!亨特小姐。
- Don't you dare touch him again! - Miss Hunter.
你!你叫你自己一个人吗?处理这人渣吗?
You! You call yourself a man? Treating with that scum?
亨特小姐,那个人是我们的敌人。
Miss Hunter, that man is our enemy.
一个词从你的任何类型和他将被射杀。明白吗?
One word from you of any kind and he will be shot. Understand?
没错,帽。
That's right, Cap.
- 我可以帮助你,小姐?- 我很能让自己。
- Can I help you, miss? - I'm quite capable of getting on by myself.
看来你需要一个小的注意力。医生!你会看我们的好朋友的耳朵?
Seems you need a little attention. Doctor! Will you look to our good friend's ear?
对不起,我有一个胃弱者。奥蒂斯,看看你能做些什么为我们的新招。
Sorry but I got a weak stomach. Otis, see what you can do for our new recruit.
很难解释一个人,不是吗?
Hard to explain a man, isn't it?
照顾这个男人。
Take care of this man.
枪伤,先生。
Gunshot wound, sir.
噢!你的目标坚持那件事清楚到对方?
Ow! You aim to stick that thing clear through to the other side?
我严重怀疑它会遇到任何阻碍。
I seriously doubt it would have met with any obstruction.
中士,给我几个那些好雪茄。
Sergeant, give me a couple of those good cigars.
噢!嘿!
Ow! Hey!
- 做了伤害你,维吉尔?- 这将使你感觉更好。
- Did it hurt you, Virgil? - This will make you feel better.
我们将有一个谈话,伙计们。你来通过牛顿站?
We'll have a talk, fellas. Did you come through Newton Station?
- 当然做了。- 任何军队吗?
- Sure did. - Any troops there?
不是没有更多的。现在,阿拉巴马州第六,它在那里。
Not no more. Now, the Alabama Sixth, it was there.
但它搬到维克斯堡与乔治亚州第十。
But it moved to Vicksburg with the Georgia Tenth.
- 第十是会让处女座非常喜欢和我的旧衣服。- “是”是正确的。
- The Tenth was Virg and my's old outfit. - "Was" is right.
我想没有任何军队在30或40英里。
I guess there aren't any troops within 30 or 40 miles.
- 60至少。- 你卑鄙的叛徒!
- 60 at least. - You vile traitors!
维克斯堡,你说呢?这就是我们前往。
Vicksburg, you say? That's where we're headed for.
看来我们正在进入一个小战斗。
Looks like we're in for a little fight.
- 谢谢,伙计们。解开警长。- 奢侈地,嗯,会让处女座非常喜欢吗?
- Thanks, fellas. Untie the sheriff. - High on the hog, huh, Virg?
嘿,看起来像你美国佬男孩做所有正确的女人。
Hey, looks like you Yankee boys do all right with the women.
和这是一个非常蓬松的一个你那里。
And that's a pretty towheaded one you've got there.
-嗨。- 你好,小姐。
- Hi. - Howdy, missy.
- 嗨,小姐。- 看看我跟你说过了北?
- Hi, missy. - See what I told you about up North?
- 中士,你的长手套。- 一个快乐,先生。
- Sergeant, your gauntlets. - A pleasure, sir.
嗨,小姐。嘿,小姐。
Hi, missy. Hey, missy.
删除这个囚犯。
Remove the prisoner.
你要打死他个人,帽吗?让杰基乔在这里做。
Are you going to shoot him personal, Cap? Let Jackie Jo here do it.
他是最好的铛射我看过。
He's the best dang shot I ever seen.
我曾经看到他拍摄一个失控的黑人奴隶的女人……
I once saw him shoot a runaway negro slave woman...
正确的通过…的眼睛。
right through the... eyes.
领带抬起来。
Tie 'em up.
警长,我将让他们在你的手中。手枪。这是加载。
Sheriff, I'll leave them in your hands. Pistol. It's loaded.
祝贺Greenbriar小姐的汉娜猎人。
With the compliments of Miss Hannah Hunter of Greenbriar.
- 谢谢您,先生。欢迎您,先生。
- Thank you, sir. - You are welcome, sir.
满意,小姐猎人吗?
Satisfied, Miss Hunter?
嗯,你的正义感并惊喜我一点。
Well, your sense of justice does surprise me a little.
正义吗?那些人会是累赘。
Justice? Those men would have been excess baggage.
我不相信他们任何超过我真的相信……
I don't trust them any more than I really trust...
- 比我吗?- 没错。
- Than me? - That's right.
是的,夫人。一个强硬的人理解。
Yes, ma'am. A hard man to understand.
牛顿站铁路连接
NEWTON STATION THE RAILROAD JUNCTION
提供了邦联在维克斯堡
SUPPLYING THE CONFEDERATE FORCES AT VICKSBURG
- 嗨,姑娘们!- 洋基!滚开!
- Hi there, girls! - Yankees! Get out of here!
走出去,你脏佬!滚开!
Get out, you dirty Yankees! Get out of here!
- 乔纳森・!亨特小姐。
- Jonathan! - Miss Hunter.
不能跟囚犯。我们有一个漂亮的房间,你上楼。
Mustn't talk to the prisoners. We've got a nice room for you upstairs.
- 给你一个热水澡。- 你可以改变你的衣服。
- A nice hot bath for you. - You can change your clothes.
你看,我们有很多工作要做。
You see, we've got a lot of work to do.
- 你不会烧镇上吗?- 没有。正义的战争物资。
- You're not going to burn the town? - No. Just war supplies.
棉花。铁路设备。违禁品,夫人。
Cotton. Railway equipment. Contraband, ma'am.
违禁品。那是我,不是吗?
Contraband. That's me, ain't it?
来吧!下马!
Come on! Dismount!
- 巧妙地做了,Richard。- 谢谢你,先生。
- Neatly done, Richard. - Thank you, sir.
- 这是整个驻军吗?- 每一个人。
- Is this the whole garrison? - Every last man.
他们放弃了没有挣扎,就像凯撒,克利奥帕特拉。
They gave up without a struggle, like Caesar to Cleopatra.
没有挣扎,嗯?
Without a struggle, huh?
科比,总部设立在这个酒店。
Kirby, set up headquarters in this hotel.
- 这将是一个快乐,先生。-并关闭酒吧。
- It would be a pleasure, sir. - And close the bar.
-是的,先生。-我们开始一天的工作吗?
- Yes, sir. - Shall we set about the day's work?
我要爱设置一个火炬,这窝叛军。
I'm going to love setting a torch to this nest of rebels.
囚犯!
Prisoner!
- 叛军上校,先生。-是的,先生?
- Rebel colonel, sir. - Yes, sir?
什么是违禁品在仓库里和那些汽车在侧线吗?
What is the contraband in the warehouses and on those cars in the sidings?
房地产的美利坚联盟国不是违禁品,先生。
The property of the Confederate States of America is not contraband, sir.
哦?
Oh?
嗯,让我们看看它从我身边,上校。
Well, let's look at it from my side, Colonel.
- 乔纳森・!乔尼英里。- 你知道上校?
- Jonathan! Jonny Miles. - You know the Colonel?
确定。我们是老朋友了。上次我们并肩战斗是印第安人。
Sure. We're old friends. Last time we served together was fighting Indians.
对不起关于手臂。什么时候的事?
Sorry about the arm. When did that happen?
我想要的不是你的关怀也回忆我们的协会。
I want neither your solicitude nor to recall our association.
有我你的许可,退休,先生?
Have I your permission to retire, sir?
把他带走。
Take him away.
我不知道一个男人像英里放弃那么简单。
I can't figure a man like Miles giving up that easy.
他是西点军校。坚决严厉的。
He's West Point. Tough as nails.
也许失去的胳膊让他心力交瘁。
Maybe losing that arm took a lot out of him.
这个人我知道可能失去双臂,仍然想踢死你。吸毒成瘾者?
The man I knew could lose both arms and still try to kick you to death. Hoppy?
-你有没有哨这整个区域?-是的,先生。
- Did you picket this whole area? - Yes, sir.
上校!有一个篮板球的火车来了,先生。
Colonel! There's a reb train coming in, sir.
西科德!伍德沃德!
Secord! Woodward!
这个酒吧的封闭。
This bar's closed.
嗯,它必须是一个供应列车-滚动到我们的圈。
Well, it must be a supply train - rolling right into our laps.
我从来没有看到一个供应列车没有守卫在它之前。
I never saw a supply train without guards on it before.
他们不会太警报在他们自己的领地。
They wouldn't be too alert in their own territory.
- 是,犹太人的尊称上校?- 《每日电讯报》的办公室。
- Where was that reb colonel? - The telegraph office.
- 电报办公室吗?-是的,先生。
- Telegraph office? - Yes, sir.
好了,德,你知道该怎么做。
All right, Secord, you know what to do.
让那些马掩护下!
Get those horses under cover!
让他们马车!
Get them wagons!
得到那散包那里。看它!
Get that bale off there. Watch it!
下来,看不见的地方。
Down, out of sight.
盖从内。
Cover from inside.
- 先生?- 不,我不需要它。
- Sir? - No, I don't need it.
- 每个人的准备动作,先生。-谢谢你。
- Everyone's ready for action, sir. - Thank you.
火!
Fire!
我不想要这个。我试图避免战斗。
I didn't want this. I tried to avoid a fight.
这就是为什么我拿起药。
That's why I took up medicine.
- 看那白痴!- 约翰尼・!乔尼英里!
- Look at that idiot! - Jonny! Jonny Miles!
停止射击!
Cease fire!
- 好吧,移动他。- 移动这个人了。
- All right, move him up. - Move this man up.
让我有帮助。我是一个医生。马文博士。
Let me be of assistance. I'm a physician. Dr Marvin.
主要的假象。我们感谢你的帮助。
Major Kendall. We appreciate your help.
这个人是下一个。
This man is next.
去得到一些空气。
Go get some air.
- 我可以帮助。- 离开。
- I can help. - Get out.
让他离开这里。
Get him out of here.
卢,你去买一些冰。所有你能找到的。
Lou, you go and get some ice. All you can find.
你太。你帮助他。快速。
You too. You help him. Quick.
你要去多久,肯德尔吗?
How long are you going to be, Kendall?
自己看一看。我们刚刚开始。
Take a look for yourself. We just started.
- 我需要一个明确的答复。-我不能给你一个。
- I need a definite answer. - I can't give you one.
我也有工作要做,你知道的。
I've got a job to do too, you know.
至少5个小时。
At least five hours.
上校。嘿,上校。
Colonel. Hey, Colonel.
你好,骑兵。
Hello, trooper.
我是霍斯金斯。巴德・霍斯金斯。
I'm Hoskins. Bud Hoskins.
K公司,先生。
K Company, sir.
- 你不认识我。- 当然我知道你。
- You don't know me. - Sure I know you.
好士兵。你只是躺容易,儿子。
Good soldier. You just lie easy, son.
我把我的手放在那里,这都是…
I put my hand on there and it's all...
躺着不动。
Just lie still.
你会写我的马,上校?她会喜欢它如果你…
You'll write my ma, Colonel? She'd love it if you...
你会写她自己不久。
You'll be writing her yourself before long.
没有。
No.
不,我知道。
No, I know.
- 我害怕,上校。- 没有什么好害怕的。
- And I'm scared, Colonel. - There's nothing to be scared of.
不,我没事。
No, I'm all right.
只是紧紧抓住我,先生。
Just hold onto me, sir.
和写我的马。
And write my ma.
我将永远在你的债务。
I'll be in your debt forever.
你不自豪吗?
Aren't you proud?
是的,我非常骄傲的那个男孩。
Yes, I'm very proud of that boy.
- 报告。- 3人死亡,18人受伤。
- Report. - Three dead, 18 wounded.
拆迁程序的命令,先生。和酒吧是封闭的。
Demolition proceeding as ordered, sir. And the bar is closed.
酒吧是开放的!
The bar is open!
得到了一些鸦片酊。-没有更多的,先生。
- Get some laudanum. - There is no more, sir.
下来的克星,除非你想走了它。
Come down out of there, buster, unless you want to go up with it.
哦,约翰,有一百万美元的铁路设备。
Well, John, there goes half a million dollars of railroad equipment.
这就是我的生活,你知道。建设铁路。
That's how I made my living, you know. Building railroads.
铁路的建成八英里!北和南……
The railroad's finished for eight miles! North and south...
约翰,你在做什么呢?等一下!
John, what are you doing? Wait a minute!
- 约翰!-出去!
- John! - Get out!
- 这是一个医院你知道吗?-听我说。
- You figure this is a hospital? - Listen to me.
和我可以做它上校,也!离开这里。
And I can do it to colonels, too! Get out of here.
当我们搬出去,给你的人- 受伤的- 很多酒。
When we move out, give your people - the wounded - a lot of liquor.
我想做的,不管怎样。
I'd do that anyway.
在这里,把这。
Here, take this.
它将稳定下来。
It will steady you down.
我从来没有见过这种方式之前。
I've never seen it this way before.
我和我的父亲死的时候。
I was with my father when he died.
但他平静地去世。
But he died peacefully.
- 没有痛苦。- 嗯,这很幸运。
- Without pain. - Well, it was lucky.
你们俩的。
For both of you.
去吧,肯德尔!忙了一整天!
Go ahead, Kendall! Have a field day!
你什么意思,一整天吗?
What do you mean, field day?
他的努力拯救人的性命。
He's fighting to save men's lives.
人的生活吗?或者他的职业的声誉吗?
Men's lives? Or the reputation of his profession?
- 你不可能是认真的,上校马洛。- 就用你的方式,夫人。
- You can't be serious, Colonel Marlowe. - Have it your way, ma'am.
- 医学是最高贵的……- 当然,崇高的职业,高贵的誓言。
- Medicine is the most noble... - Sure, noble profession, noble oath.
灯笼上举行高。所以高他们不会承认他们在琢磨……
Lanterns held on high. So high they won't admit they're groping for...
- 你不公平和…- 不公平?
- You're unfair and... - Unfair?
有一个女孩没有多少龄比那个男孩在那里。
There was a girl not much older than that boy in there.
我不是不公平之后,明白吗?
I wasn't unfair then, understand?
因为他们使用了很多华丽的词语,一个部分的手不会理解。
Because they used a lot of fancy words that a section hand wouldn't understand.
所以我把她抱下来而他们工作的两个她。
So I held her down while two of 'em worked on her.
我信任的医生然后。相信他们。
I trusted doctors then. Believed in 'em.
因为我在爱,我不想看到她死。
Because I was in love and I didn't want to see her die.
一个肿瘤,他们说这是。
A tumour, they said it was.
和它必须马上出来。
And it had to come out right away.
所以他们把皮带在她的嘴,她能咬掉她的尖叫声
So they stuck a leather strap in her mouth so she could bite off her screams
虽然他们切掉到那里。
while they cut away to get in there.
和他们发现了什么?没有什么!
And what did they find? Nothing!
哦,抱歉。当然,他们犯了一个错误。
Oh, they were sorry. Sure, they'd made a mistake.
他们谈论的话题,在他们接下来的实验。
They had something to talk about before their next experiment.
可是我呢?他们让我乞求她不要死去。
But what about me? They left me begging her not to die.
我失去了我的妻子。
I lost my wife.
我没有杀不是其中之一。
I didn't kill either one of them.
我一定是疯了,或者太传统。
I must have been crazy, or too conventional.
相当一个演讲。我想我的感觉我的酒。
Quite a speech. I guess I'm feeling my liquor.
哇!
Whoo!
- 谢谢你,医生。- 欢迎你,夫人。
- Thank you, Doctor. - You're welcome, ma'am.
谢谢,汉克。
Thanks, Hank.
-嗯,我们几乎愚弄你。- 几乎。
- Well, we almost fooled you. - Almost.
你永远不会使它,汉克。他们已经接近你。
You'll never make it, Hank. They're already closing in on you.
贝德福德森林是嗅探你的高跟鞋。
Bedford Forest is sniffing at your heels.
你直奔安德森威尔监狱的。
You're headed straight for that prison at Andersonville.
没有什么我们可以做的来帮助你。韩国正在挨饿。
There's nothing we can do to help you there. The South is starving.
乔纳森,我所做的一切都是行医。
Jonathan, all I'm doing is practising medicine.
老ironhead确实所有的思维。
Old ironhead does all the thinking.
他认为事情很好。西点军校吗?
He thinks things pretty good. West Point?
不,部分的手。
No, section hand.
- 苏珊和孩子们是如何?- 他们很好。
- How are Susan and the kids? - They're fine.
在维克斯堡。我希望你很快就会看到他们。
In Vicksburg. I expect you'll be seeing them soon.
不错的尝试,乔纳森。不错的尝试。
Nice try, Jonathan. Nice try.
看到你在维克斯堡,吸毒成瘾者。
See you in Vicksburg, Hoppy.
- 再见,吸毒成瘾者。- 再见,大夫。
- Goodbye, Hoppy. - Goodbye, Doctor.
我想谢谢你所有我学到。
I want to thank you for all I've learned.
我会努力活着回家多达我可以。
I shall endeavour to get home alive as many as I can.
你是一个好男人,吸毒成瘾者。
You're a good man, Hoppy.
这事以后都结束了,如果我们不见面,一定和从医学院毕业了。
After this thing is all over, if we don't meet again, be sure and finish medical school.
我要强调它,先生。
I shall make a point of it, sir.
再见,大夫。,祝你好运。
Goodbye, Doctor. And good luck.
谢谢你,医生,为你所有的帮助。
Thank you, Doctor, for all your help.
维克斯堡。他们要去西南到巴吞鲁日。
Vicksburg. They're headed southwest to Baton Rouge.
巴吞鲁日。
Baton Rouge.
这是巴吞鲁日,主要的。跟一般的森林。
It's Baton Rouge, Major. Tell General Forest.
是的,你可以。我在调查委员会。我知道能做些什么。
Yes, you can. I'm on the board of inquiry. I know exactly what can be done.
现在,他没有权利,甚至作为一个…
Now, he has no right, even as a...
- 菲尔……- 是的,约翰?
- Phil... - Yes, John?
我很抱歉发生了什么回到牛顿站。
I'm sorry about what happened back at Newton Station.
忘记它,约翰。你是在一个应变。
Forget it, John. You were under a strain.
但是自从你提出这个话题……
But since you brought up the subject...
你知道,约翰,我是比你长的人。
You know, John, I'm an older man than you are.
更重要的是,我是一个政治家。
What's more, I'm a politician.
我们已经打翻了牛顿站。
We've knocked over Newton Station.
这是一个光荣的事情在我的…我们的记录。
It's a glorious thing on my... our records.
但现在是时候北上,回到洛杉矶田庄……
But now is the time to head north, back to La Grange...
我们承诺,菲尔,这就是事实。
We're committed, Phil, and that's that.
固执。固执!
Stubborn. Stubborn!
哎哟。
Ouch.
我能有一些酒吞下,医生?
Can I have some of that liquor to swallow, Doc?
你没有一个好足够的借口。这是怎么发生的,Dunker吗?
You haven't got a good enough excuse. How'd this happen, Dunker?
我被砍其中一个电线杆在牛顿回到那里。
I was chopping down one of them telegraph poles back there in Newton.
- 右到我的腿斧反弹。-
- The axe ricocheted right onto my leg. -
- 去逮捕斧头。- 它根本没有什么。
- Go arrest the axe. - It ain't nothing.
没什么,嗯?几乎血液中毒。你很幸运我看到你一瘸一拐的。
Nothing, huh? Almost blood poisoning. You're lucky I saw you limping.
噢,医生……
Aw, Doc...
你将在那里?污垢?
What are you putting on there? Dirt?
树苔。普通的绿色模具。它有一些类型的愈合剂,我想象。
Tree moss. Ordinary green mould. It has some sort of healing agent, I imagine.
- 你想象?- 我不想象结果,上校。
- You imagine? - I don't imagine the results, Colonel.
这是一个古老的夏延印度治愈。
This is an old Cheyenne Indian cure.
啧啧!夏安族印第安人治愈!
Tsk! Cheyenne Indian cure!
绿色模具!树苔!
Green mould! Tree moss!
你一直在。向我报告任何疼痛。
You keep this on. Report any soreness to me.
Lukey !
Lukey!
- 因为他们向我开枪,我想念汉娜?- 没关系。
- What for they shoot me, Miss Hannah? - It's all right.
得到我的包。
Get my bag.
-她走了,夫人。-哦,不。
- She's gone, ma'am. - Oh, no.
你还好吗,想念汉娜?
Are you all right, Miss Hannah?
我给你带了一个小片断的块的蜡烛。
I brought you a little bitty piece of candle.
我们还会有一些热水给你在早上。
We'll have some hot water for you in the morning.
和看哪!在这里。我发现了一块镜子给你。
And lookee here. I found a piece of looking glass for you.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我希望你能…可以在这里休息一下。
I hope you'll... be able to get some rest here.
你必须知道我们如何感觉,夫人,大约Lukey。
You must know how we feel, ma'am, about Lukey.
我们多么遗憾……
How much we regret...
我对你的歉意……
how sorry I am...
在某些方面,我们的原因……
that in some way we were the cause of...
Lukey不是要求那。
Lukey isn't asking for that.
我希望我能让你走。
I wish I could let you go.
如果我给你一匹马,让你走,
If I gave you a horse and let you go,
你答应我不要告诉任何人我们的计划在接下来的24小时?
would you promise not to tell anybody our plans for the next 24 hours?
太晚了。
It's too late.
太迟了,所有的。
It's too late for all of that.
没有更多的承诺。
No more promises.
现在没有更多的东西。
No more anything now.
我很抱歉。真的很抱歉。
I'm sorry. Truly sorry.
Dunker。
Dunker.
哎呀!
Agh!
- 这是所有正确的昨天的腿。- 是的,但是今天早上它有swolled。
- That leg was all right yesterday. - Yes, but this morning it got swolled.
- 我不得不撕我的裤腿。- 泥敷在哪里?
- I had to tear my trouser leg. - Where's the poultice?
它开始进入瘙痒,先生,所以我就把她关闭。
It started into itching, sir, so I just yanked her off.
这是一个签字开始愈合,你这个傻瓜。
It was a sign it was beginning to heal, you fool.
来到这里,否则你就麻烦了。
Come in here, or you're in trouble.
布朗,伸出援手。
Brown, lend a hand.
在那边。
Over there.
-咖啡?- 谢谢。
- Coffee? - Thanks.
报告。
Report.
这是盐温泉,好的,先生。连一个士兵里面,无论是。
That's Salt Springs, all right, sir. Nary a soldier inside, neither.
只是一些老女人,一对盐工厂和一所学校的小男孩。
Just some old women, a couple of salt mills and a school for little boys.
-盐米尔斯需要燃烧。- 为什么展示自己?我们已经是幸运的了。
- The salt mills will need burning. - Why show ourselves? We've been lucky.
你叫那咖啡吗?
You call that coffee?
我们不能通过它。盐是一样重要的弹药。
We can't pass 'em up. Salt is as valuable as ammunition.
我们将在这里露营地打击他们,在早上。
We'll bivouac here and hit them in the morning.
好吧,你是老板。
All right, you're the boss.
你好哦,下来我们去那里不是没有这样的词是“不能”……
Hi-ho, down we go There ain't no such word as "can't"...
- 怎么了?- 医生的工作在Dunker的腿。
- What's going on? - The doctor's working on Dunker's leg.
我离开了我的爱我的爱我离开……
I left my love My love I left...
再拉。
Take another pull.
啊,那很好商店酒、Doc。谁打了约翰?
Ah, that's good store liquor, Doc. Who hit John?
- 我要把它脱下来,Dunker。- 你说了什么?
- I've got to take it off, Dunker. - What did you say?
我要把你的腿了。
I've got to take your leg off.
你要什么?
You've got to what?
毒的太过分了。你会死在早上。
The poison's gone too far. You'll be dead by morning.
什么可以来的我之后,医生?一条腿吗?我什么能来了吗?
What can come of me after that, Doc? One leg? What can come of me after that?
我将钻机吊索具及留给你最接近的平民关怀。
I'll rig a sling and leave you with the closest civilian care.
平民在乎吗?
Civilian care?
然后是监狱接下来,嗯?安德森威尔?
Then comes prison next, huh? Andersonville?
这是发生在我身上,医生? !
Is that what happens to me, Doc?!
- 很可能。- 是的。
- Quite possibly. - Yeah.
这是一个地狱的一个艰难的选择,一个小伙子必须作出。
That's a hell of a tough choice for a fella to have to make.
- 不是吗?嗯,告诉我。不是吗?- 它必须去掉。
- Ain't it? Well, tell me. Ain't it? - It's got to come off.
所有的权利。
All right.
你只是不停地射击。
You just fire away.
但在你开始锯切,你给我一些东西,氯仿。
But before you start sawing, you give me some of that chloroform stuff.
- 你把我,医生。- 我给你我得到了什么。
- You put me out, Doc. - I'll give you what I got.
现在咬人。给我一个手在这里。抱他下来。
Now bite this. Give me a hand here. Hold him down.
上帝……上帝!
God... God!
杰斐逊军事学院
JEFFERSON MILITARY ACADEMY
显然它是列那突袭了牛顿站。
It's obviously the column that raided Newton Station.
维克斯堡,报告只是一个微弱的。
That Vicksburg report was just a faint.
我以为一队骑兵是由于这里。
I thought a brigade of cavalry was due here.
- 他们不会在这里直到今天晚些时候,先生。-你所建议的是最极端的。
- They won't get here till late today, sir. - What you suggest is most extreme.
- 我的长的男孩在这里只有16。- 该死,先生!
- My oldest boy here is only 16. - Damn it, sir!
我请求你的原谅,上校。我的意思是,尊敬的…
I beg your pardon, Colonel. I mean, Reverend...
看,我有一个男孩在我的电池这是14,一个男人那是72。这是一场战争,先生。
Look, I've got a boy in my battery that's 14, a man that's 72. This is a war, sir.
我可以开始吊在他们生物弹片和葡萄,赶上他们午睡。
I could start lobbing shrapnel and grape at them critters, catch 'em napping.
只是一个展示武力,那么也许我们可以抵御它们直到骑兵找到这里。
Just a show of force, then perhaps we can hold them off until the cavalry gets here.
- 学员主要巴克斯代尔。- 先生?
- Cadet Major Barksdale. - Sir?
组装你的营。整个补充。
Assemble your battalion. The entire complement.
泰勒和Fitcher有腮腺炎。
Taylor and Fitcher have the mumps.
把他们从值勤表。嗯,你听到了中尉。
Scratch them from the duty roster. Well, you heard the Lieutenant.
你会很高兴通知队我们将在黎明。
You'll be pleased to inform the corps we shall move at dawn.
谢谢你,先生!
Thank you, sir!
注意!
Attention!
学员主要巴克斯代尔,你可以向前移动你的专栏。和上帝保佑你。
Cadet Major Barksdale, you may move your column forward. And God bless you.
右肩、手臂!
Right shoulder, arms!
正确的,脸!
Right, face!
学员,前进!
Cadets, forward march!
牧师,我的小男孩约翰尼。他是我的一切离开。
Reverend, my boy Johnny. He's all I've got left.
首先他的爸爸,然后他的叔叔,他的兄弟。现在他吗?
First his pa, then his uncles, his brothers. Now him?
他的一切我已经离开,尊敬的。我不会让他走。
He's all I have left, Reverend. I'm not going to let him go.
学员鼓手布福德,你解除责任。
Cadet drummer Buford, you are relieved of duty.
我想节省一点,对于Dunker。
I'd save a little of that for Dunker.
我只是失去了他。
I just lost him.
你失去了Dunker,嗯?
You lost Dunker, eh?
嗯,你失去了我们一个很好的人。
Well, you lost us a good man.
血液中毒。截肢。震撼的心,我想。
Blood poisoning. Amputation. A shock to the heart, I guess.
- 我不会不得不截肢如果他想……- 如果,也许,也许。
- I wouldn't have had to amputate if he'd... - If, maybe, perhaps.
- 怎么了,巫医吗?-部分的手,我有你!
- What's the matter, medicine man? - Section hand, I've had you!
带你的衬衫!
Strip your blouse!
我认为你是对的。来吧。
I think you're right. Come on.
有序!马!把抬起来!
Orderly! Horses! Bring 'em up!
约翰尼!
Johnny!
约翰尼・布福德!
Johnny Buford!
约翰尼!
Johnny!
- 有什么规则,上校?只是做你自己。
- What are the rules, Colonel? - Just make up your own.
你说没有规则,上校。
You said no rules, Colonel.
在你的脚上,嘎声。
On your feet, croaker.
火彼得!
Fire Peter!
火保罗!
Fire Paul!
炮火,先生。隐藏的电池。
Artillery fire, sir. Hidden battery.
那些只不过是孩子。男生。
Those are nothing but children. Schoolboys.
- 只是有些孩子从军事学校。- 但他们不断。
- Just some kids from the military school. - But they keep coming.
声音装配。
Sound assembly.
至少这圣乔不是没有孩子。
At least that Holy Joe ain't no kid.
停止!前列,跪下!
Halt! Front rank, kneel!
- 准备好了!亨特小姐……
- Ready! - Miss Hunter...
的目的!火!
Aim! Fire!
后排名,停止!
Rear rank, halt!
跪了!
Kneel!
准备好了!的目的!火!
Ready! Aim! Fire!
你想做什么?建立野战医院的吗?
What do you want to do? Set up a field hospital?
是的,现在你要做什么?
Yes, what are you going to do now?
恕我直言,我要滚开。
With all due respect, I'm going to get the hell out of here.
声音回忆!
Sound recall!
我告诉你照顾这个女人!
I told you to take care of this woman!
上校,我买了一个囚犯。你想要什么我做什么和他在一起吗?
Colonel, I got me a prisoner. What do you want me to do with him?
- 揍他。- 在底部?
- Spank him. - On the bottom?
你认为呢?
Where do you think?
- 停止!- 抓住它,上校。
- Halt! - Hold it, Colonel.
- 报告。-个篮板。他们得到了整个道路封锁。
- Report. - Rebs. They got the whole road blocked.
- 有多少?- 一个完整的团的常客,先生。
- How many? - A full regiment of regulars, sir.
他们有两张大炮和他们挖在沿着这条路。
They got two pieces of artillery and they're digging in along the road.
唯一要做的就是冲回盐温泉和向东。
The only thing to do is fight our way back to Salt Springs and head east.
- 你没有看见,尘埃?- 骑兵。我们三个小时后。
- Haven't you seen that dust? - Cavalry. Following us for three hours.
上校,执事说他知道这个国家真正的好。不要你,执事?
Colonel, the deacon says he knows this country real good. Don't you, Deacon?
传讲福音,歌颂耶和华在这一带多。
Preaching the gospel, singing the praises of the Lord hereabouts for years.
这可能是一个好主意,现在开始祈祷。
It might be a good idea to start praying right now.
那个执事走私逃跑的奴隶北出去穿过沼泽。
The deacon smuggled runaway slaves north out of here through the swamp.
- 与地下铁路。- 你能走私我们南吗?
- With the underground railway. - Could you smuggle us out south?
等待一分钟。等待一分钟。
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
为什么,那沼泽充满流沙,响尾蛇……
Why, that swamp is full of quicksand, rattlers...
伊甸园有其忍耐太。
The Garden of Eden had its sufferance too.
跟着我,哥哥上校,穿过沼泽到河Amite。
Follow me, brother Colonel, through the swamps all the way to the river Amite.
领导和蔼,主啊。
Lead kindly, Lord.
好吧,给自己几个新鲜的马。
All right, get yourself a couple of fresh horses.
通过正确的侧面,隐蔽。
By the right flank, take cover.
来吧!
Come on!
来吧!来吧!
Come on! Come on!
搬出去。来吧,男孩。
Move out. Come on, boy.
来吧,男孩。
Come on, boy.
继续前进!继续前进!来吧!
Keep moving! Keep moving! Come on!
继续前进。保持清醒,孩子。
Keep moving. Stay awake there, kid.
继续前进。捡起你的脚。
Keep moving. Pick up your feet.
约翰,有多远你图到巴吞鲁日吗?
John, how far do you figure to Baton Rouge?
40英里。
40 miles.
保持生机!
Keep alive in there!
- 你要我道歉现在或以后吗?- 为了什么?
- You want me to apologise now or later? - For what?
- 继续前进!-我从来没有想过你可以做它。
- Keep moving! - I never thought you could do it.
你知道,约翰,我已经放弃了所有想竞选国会。
You know, John, I've given up all thought of running for Congress.
这个在我的记录,由乔治,我能成为州长。
With this on my record, by George, I can be Governor.
- 继续前进!- 密歇根州州长。
- Keep moving! - Governor of Michigan.
你能说出你自己的工作。铁路专员……
And you can name your own job. Railroad commissioner...
不要开始竞选承诺直到我们到达那里。加入你们的团。
Don't start making campaign promises till we get there. Join your regiment.
上校,我的责任,从医学上来讲,是为了通知您
Colonel, my duty, medically speaking, is to inform you
这些人可能会在他们的手和膝盖。
that these men may make it on their hands and knees.
我们已经20小时没有停止。我们需要休息。
We've been 20 hours without a stop. We need a rest.
我有眼睛,假象。
I've got eyes, Kendall.
这也是我的责任通知你,如果我们遇到一个战斗……
It's also my duty to inform you that if we run into a fight...
这是所有的,医生。
That is all, Doctor.
谢谢你,先生。
Thank you, sir.
列,停止!
Column, halt!
-伍德沃德。- 哟!
- Woodward. - Yo!
第一小队,球探桥的另一边。
First squad, scout the other side of the bridge.
第一小队,向前,哟!
First squad, forward, yo!
我不知道你是否听说过。
I don't know if you've heard.
你的人在我们身后大约一个小时,会很快来临。
Your people are about an hour behind us, coming fast.
我听说过。
I've heard.
我们要到巴吞鲁日。我们会把你留在这儿。
We're going on to Baton Rouge. We'll leave you here.
你自己的类可以照顾你。
Your own kind can take care of you.
- 我肯定他们能。- 是的。
- I'm sure they can. - Yes.
我…
I...
我很抱歉对于苦难和…
I'm sorry for the hardship and...
的屈辱,我们……那我给你。
the humiliation that we've... that I've caused you.
让她离开这里!
Get her out of here!
回忆!
Recall!
让她在那个小屋!
Get her in that cabin!
来吧,想念汉娜。
Come on, Miss Hannah.
看起来他们已经得到了我们在一个陷阱。
Looks like they've got us in a trap.
敲它!
Knock on it!
给我们一些封面!
Give us some cover!
队长伍德沃德,前进!
Captain Woodward, move!
别管我。
Leave me alone.
我一切都好。让我独自一人,你会吗?
I'm all right. Let me alone, would you?
容易的。
Easy.
西科德上校马上得到。不是这样,其他的门。
Get Colonel Secord right away. Not that way, the other door.
- 报告。- 这是充满着个篮板。至少两炮。
- Report. - It's alive with rebs. At least two cannons.
- 他们跳我们这么快。- 步兵?
- They jumped us so quick. - Infantry?
-伍德充满他们。- 加入您的队伍。
- The wood's full of 'em. - Join your troop.
- 削减他的引导下,山姆。- 没有人的切割,引导。
- Cut his boot off, Sam. - Nobody's cutting that boot off.
削减他的引导。
Cut his boot off.
采取一个好的僵硬的震动。
Take a good stiff jolt.
那些是20美元的靴子,骑兵。
Those are $20 boots, trooper.
得到了一些水。-谁,我吗?
- Get some water. - Who, me?
带一个队伍,牧师,或他的任何东西。
Take A-troop and that reverend, or whatever he is.
找到一个福特好歹在河。旁边的em。采取一个喇叭手与你。
Find a ford someway across that river. Flank 'em. Take a bugler with you.
先生,谢谢你的机会。
Sir, thank you for the opportunity.
约翰,这是一个陷阱。他们希望我们能够跨越这桥。
John, it's a trap. They want us to cross that bridge.
它就像经历一个漏斗。
It'd be like going through a funnel.
在这样的位置,没有什么可耻的关于尊贵的投降。
In a position like this, there's nothing disgraceful about honourable surrender.
回到你的队伍。让他们在盖。
Get back to your troop. Keep 'em under cover.
-你的意思…你是怎么回事?,滚出去!
- You mean... you're going on? - Get out of here!
你不会在你目前这颗子弹。
You're not going far with that bullet in you.
你把你自己的甜蜜时间削减它从那里。
You're taking your own sweet time about cutting it out of there.
你不是唯一受伤的人在这里,上校。把我的包。
You're not the only wounded man here, Colonel. Get me my bag.
现在,这是要有点痛。
Now, this is going to hurt a little.
继续它,假象。
Go on with it, Kendall.
- 哦!- 保持腿伸展。
- Ooh! - Keep that leg stretched.
探头,请。
Probe, please.
(马洛唧唧的声音)
(Marlowe yelps)
你过得愉快吗?
Are you having fun?
你是幸运的。
You're lucky.
你可能不相信,但我买的上校,你一些时间。
You may not believe it, Colonel, but I bought you some time.
- 几个小时吗?- 也许更多。
- A couple of hours? - Maybe more.
谢谢。
Thanks.
- 第一个密歇根位置,先生。-第一伊利诺斯州的位置。我们是第一。
- First Michigan in position, sir. - First Illinois in position. We were first.
我一切都好。
I'm all right.
开始移动。
Get cracking.
全能的上帝。他来。
God Almighty. Here he comes.
上升。
Mount up.
你听见我,柯比。上升。
You heard me, Kirby. Mount up.
你听到了上校!上升!
You heard the Colonel! Mount up!
上校。
Colonel.
那个执事找到地方福特。男人应该在现在的位置。
The deacon found a place to ford. The men ought to be in position by now.
谢谢。盖我们的后方。看看我们有多少时间。
Thanks. Cover our rear. See how much time we've got.
是的,先生。
Yes, sir.
- 你的马?- 回到了沼泽,先生。
- Where's your horse? - Back in the swamp, sir.
- 嘴唇干燥吗?-是的,先生。但我的喇叭不是。
- Lips dry? - Yes, sir. But my bugle ain't.
- 暴露的颜色。- 你听到他。
- Uncase the colours. - You heard him.
- 你知道你的订单?- 你不适合。让我带领这个费用。
- You know your orders? - You're not fit. Let me lead this charge.
有这样的成功,我可以在白宫的土地。
With a success like this, I could land in the White House.
- 我们可能会所有土地……-
- We'll probably all land in the... -
回到你的团!
Get back to your regiment!
喇叭手,声音充电!
Bugler, sound charge!
转发!火保罗。
Forwards! Fire Paul.
公司!
Company!
你受伤了,先生。
You're hurt, sir.
吹……喇叭,吹。
Blow... Trumpet, blow.
他们不能放弃。
They can't give up.
也许是疯了,也许是勇敢的。不要问我解释它。没有人可以。
Maybe it's crazy, maybe it's brave. Don't ask me to explain it. Nobody can.
来吧,我们会有很多工作要做。
Come on, we're going to have a lot of work to do.
喇叭手,声音回忆。
Bugler, sound recall.
有更多的吗?
Got any more?
来吧,给我们一些更多的。
Come on, give us some more.
多久,警官?军士长。
How much longer, Sergeant? Sergeant Major.
- 相当接近准备好了,先生。-好吧,孩子们!快点!躺在!
- Pretty near ready, sir. - All right, boys! Hurry it up! Lay it in!
敲它!
Knock on it!
快点出来!离开那里!
Come on out! Get out of there!
这些男人被感动,可以吗?- 他们都是至关重要的。
- Can those men be moved? - They're all critical.
- 我可以和他们说话吗?-我宁愿你没有。
- May I speak to them? - I'd rather you didn't.
他们必须保持安静。我已经给了他们所有的鸦片酊我有。
They've got to be quiet. I've given them all the laudanum I have.
这是一个糟糕的完成好男人。
It's a lousy finish for good men.
将会有一个医生和篮板球的列。让你的马。
There'll be a medic with that reb column. Get your horse.
我不能指望那个。
I can't count on that.
你的意思是你要住吗?
You mean you're staying?
- 药就是你找到它。- 即使是在安德森威尔?
- Medicine's where you find it. - Even in Andersonville?
即使在安德森威尔。
Even in Andersonville.
我不会怪你如果你耳光了。握手吗?
I wouldn't blame you if you slap it away. Shake hands?
- 医生,主要的灰色。- 好吧,未来。
- Doctor, Major Gray. - All right, coming.
当你的下一个医生需要绷带……
When your next doctor takes that bandage off...
我知道。树苔。
I know. Tree moss.
那么长,嘎声。
So longer, croaker.
保重,部分的手。
Take care, section hand.
你累了。你帮了很多。感谢它。
You're tired. You've helped a lot. Thanks for it.
一个糟糕的感恩之后我已经为您接通。
A poor way of being grateful after what I've put you through.
- 你最好去。- 是的,我想我最好。
- You'd better be going. - Yes, I guess I'd better.
看,汉娜猎人。
Look, Hannah Hunter.
感谢上帝我不会伤害你的原因任何更多的。
Thank God I won't be the cause of hurting you any more.
因为它发生的我爱上了你。
Because it happens I'm in love with you.
告诉她当你回来休息。
Tell her the rest when you get back.
- 你自己的,先生。-走。
- One of your own, sir. - Get going.
上校,他们对我的尾巴。
Colonel, they're right on my tail.
让我们去。
Let's go.
医生,可能我们的团的外科医生会为您服务的吗?
Doctor, could our regimental surgeon be of any service to you?
我将十分感激。
I'd be grateful.